<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-02-06T03:04:50+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/feed.xml</id><title type="html">myBlog || Trevour || demo</title><subtitle>This is a sample blog built by Trevour Chidoti using Jekyll, it uses the minimal mistakes jekyll theme Feel free to look around </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Indentity Crisis - FIRST DRAFT</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/draft/2022/02/05/identitfy-crisis.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Indentity Crisis - FIRST DRAFT" /><published>2022-02-05T22:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-02-05T22:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/draft/2022/02/05/identitfy-crisis</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/draft/2022/02/05/identitfy-crisis.html">&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is blogging A good way to make a living in Zimbabwe? Yes No Maybe IDK.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How does where you stay affect your financial well being?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How valuable is that degree anyway?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Who am I?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are we all doomed to fail because of the environment we were born in?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;And where does science and scientific thinking come into all of this?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should i be saving now for the future even if i am like 25 and broke?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should i register business?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How do i register a business from anywhere in Zimbabwe&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;whats name should you use on your personal blog?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Should you apply double entry book keeping to your personal finances?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is the Zimbabwe banking and financial system doing more good or bad for its customers?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;how much should you care about your caloric intake?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;is calory counter even worth it?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;marriage? is it worth it?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;loneliness, is it real?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;dieting, does it work?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;love is it real?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;sex, is it the ultimate form of pleasure?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;money, is it the solution to all your life’s problems?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;drugs. should you try them?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;budgets do they really save money?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;groceries, are they stealing all your money?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;degree, is it worth it?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="draft" /><summary type="html">Is blogging A good way to make a living in Zimbabwe? Yes No Maybe IDK. How does where you stay affect your financial well being? How valuable is that degree anyway? Who am I? Are we all doomed to fail because of the environment we were born in? And where does science and scientific thinking come into all of this? Should i be saving now for the future even if i am like 25 and broke? Should i register business? How do i register a business from anywhere in Zimbabwe whats name should you use on your personal blog? Should you apply double entry book keeping to your personal finances? Is the Zimbabwe banking and financial system doing more good or bad for its customers? how much should you care about your caloric intake? is calory counter even worth it? marriage? is it worth it? loneliness, is it real? dieting, does it work? love is it real? sex, is it the ultimate form of pleasure? money, is it the solution to all your life’s problems? drugs. should you try them? budgets do they really save money? groceries, are they stealing all your money? degree, is it worth it?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to myBlog</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/about/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to myBlog" /><published>2022-02-05T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2022-02-05T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/welcome-to-myBlog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/myblog/not-main/about/">&lt;p&gt;Hello and welcome. My name is Trevour Chidoti and this is myBlog. This blog is about science, creativity, health, personal finance and every other aspect of adult life, from a Zimbabwean pespective of course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&quot;about-me--trevour&quot;&gt;About Me || Trevour&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a man, 26 years old and I live in Harare, Zimbabwe. Currently I am studying aeronautical engineering at the University of Zimbabwe. I am doing my third year and hopefully I will graduate in 2024. Oh and I am also a programmer. When I am not studying, I will be writing computer programs, web-apps and games too. In fact I built this blog from scratch using the Github website and Jekyll. It’s part of a long running list of computer programs I am working on. 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/traelincoln/myblog/tree/not-main&quot;&gt;You can check out the code base on Github.&lt;/a&gt; What can I say, I like to learn!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;so-why-do-i-have-a-blog&quot;&gt;So, Why do I have a blog?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been planning on creatting a blog for a while now. I’ve often felt like I have a lot more to say than what social media (WhatsApp status to be specific) allows. I have come to the conclusion that those places aren’t the right place for me to share my thoughts in healthy way. So I have decided to create my own a little corner on the internet where healthy and creative ideas can thrive, and you’ve found it! Congratulations! But I don’t just want to share my ideas alone, thats no fun. I want to hear your thoughts too. I would like for us to explore ideas together. So, you can hit me up on Twitter and and even instagram, and we can collaborate. Or on Whatsapp if you’re a close friend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;what-am-i-going-to-blog-about&quot;&gt;What am I going to blog About?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to write about life, life in general, life unabridged, unfiltered, rough and plain and dirty. My goal for this blog is I would like to see how i can incorperate scientific thinking and writing into everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;im-inspired&quot;&gt;I’m Inspired&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am inspired by some of the podcasts that i listen to like No stupid questions, Freakonomics and Planet Money, because they often approach both serious and sometimes silly questions, and then they manage to pull out data and scientific research about those topics and come to some very interesting conclusions about life in general. Honestly, it blows my mind how having the right mindset and correct tool can influence one’s opinion and perspectives. 
So, Like I said, have decided to create this platform where you and I too can try to look at some data, analyse it critically using the scientific method and make some meaningful conclusion. And still be fun and creative. I am no professional yet, but I am still very interested in seeing what a data driven scientific approach to daily life can yield, especially using local Zimbabwean data.  And because I am not an expect, where I dont know i am going to ask, and you can correct me when you think I’m wrong. So, I look forward to some really fun and creative experimentation with data scientific writing and thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;about-the-name&quot;&gt;About the Name&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BTW, I dont have a official name for myBlog yet, thats’s why its literally called myBlog || Trevour.  But, I  am hoping that &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can help me figure that out in my next and first interactive post &lt;a href=&quot;/draft/2022/02/05/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;IDENTITY CRISIS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;which comes out next Friday at Midnight. 
Again my name is Trevour this is myBlog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website was made using Jekyll, you can find the source code for Jekyll at GitHub: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt; /
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello and welcome. My name is Trevour Chidoti and this is myBlog. This blog is about science, creativity, health, personal finance and every other aspect of adult life, from a Zimbabwean pespective of course. About Me || Trevour I am a man, 26 years old and I live in Harare, Zimbabwe. Currently I am studying aeronautical engineering at the University of Zimbabwe. I am doing my third year and hopefully I will graduate in 2024. Oh and I am also a programmer. When I am not studying, I will be writing computer programs, web-apps and games too. In fact I built this blog from scratch using the Github website and Jekyll. It’s part of a long running list of computer programs I am working on. You can check out the code base on Github. What can I say, I like to learn!</summary></entry></feed>